- Your card is...
你的牌是...
The Six of Spades!
黑桃六！
[all groan]
[大家叹气]
- It was the King of Hearts.
是红心K。
- That's what I said.
我就是这么说的。
The King of Hearts.
红心K。
- Impossible!
不可能！
- Oh, stop. Thank you.
哦，别说了。谢谢。
- I know you're excited to see me.
我知道你见到我很兴奋。
No applause necessary.
不需要掌声。
- It's not for you.
- 这不是给你的。
Tess, this is our sister, Dawn.
泰丝，这是我们的妹妹，道恩。
Tess is new.
泰丝是新来的。
- And wowsome. That's wow and awesome.
- 而且超赞。就是哇和棒极了的意思。
I made it up.
我发明的。
- Impossible.
- 不可能。
- Hi. I see you've met my brothers.
- 嗨。看来你已经见过我的兄弟们了。
I'll distract them, you run for your life.
我会分散他们的注意力，你快逃命吧。
- Don't listen to her. We're funtastic.
- 别听她的。我们超有趣的。
- You know what is else is funtastic?
- 你知道还有什么超有趣的吗？
Dawn's shirt. Talk about wowsome.
黎明的衬衫。真是令人惊叹。
- My words are catching on.
- 我的话开始流行起来了。
I should publish a Dicky-tionary.
我应该出版一本迪基词典。
- Wow, the Harper quadruplets are officially
- 哇，哈珀四胞胎正式成为
the coolest kids ever!
史上最酷的孩子！
- Isn't she great?
- 她是不是很棒？
- Wait. What's this?
- 等等。这是什么？
- Inconceivable!
- 难以置信！
- Five bucks for the candy machine.
- 五块钱买糖果机。
Hope everyone likes nutty fudge bombs.
希望大家都喜欢坚果软糖炸弹。
- She's perfect.
- 她完美无瑕。
- She's radcredible.
- 她不可思议。
- She's magic.
- 她有魔力。
- She's got to go.
- 她必须离开。
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 嘿！ ♪
[whistling melody]
♪ ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四 ♪
[whistling melody]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪
一，二
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
一，二，三，四
- What are you talking about?
你在说什么呢？
Tess is perfect!
Tess完美无缺！
- Too perfect. I'm telling you,
太完美了。我告诉你，
there's something up with that girl.
那个女孩有点不对劲。
- You also told me when I was four
- 你也在我四岁的时候告诉我
that a little man lived in my butt
我的屁股里住着一个小人
and cut my poops with a saw. - [laughs]
他用锯子割我的便便。 - [笑]
You were scared to go for like a month.
你害怕了一个月都不敢去。
- I swear I could hear him sawing!
- 我发誓我能听到他在锯！
- This is different than Poop-Saw Man.
- 这和便便锯人不一样。
She's fooling you guys.
她在骗你们。
She's a total phony fake-face.
她是个彻头彻尾的假面人。
- Ooh, I hate fake-faces!
- 哦，我讨厌假面人！
Who's a fake-face?
谁是假面人？
Is it that new girl in the camping section?
是露营区新来的那个女孩吗？
'Cause I'm always like, "Hi!" and she's always like--
因为我总是像，“嗨！”而她总是像——
- Uh, that's a mannequin.
- 呃，那是个假人模特。
- That explains why she doesn't talk.
- 难怪她不说话。
Or blink.
也不眨眼。
And smells like plastic.
还闻起来像塑料。
- Well, you're wrong.
- 好吧，你错了。
Tess is not a fake-face.
泰丝不是假面人。
- Yes, she is. Trust me,
- 不，她是。相信我，
my "chickstincts" are never wrong.
我的“直觉”从不出错。
- Our "dudestincts" are saying they are.
- 我们的“兄弟直觉”告诉我们他们是。
- Hey, kiddos. - Mom, back me up here.
- 嘿，孩子们。 - 妈妈，支持我一下。
We met this new girl at school and she's totally evil.
我们在学校遇到了这个新女孩，她绝对是邪恶的。
- She's not evil.
- 她不是邪恶的。
- I'm telling you, Tess is not what she seems.
- 我告诉你，泰丝不是她表面上那样。
I mean, she likes all four of us.
我的意思是，她喜欢我们四个。
Nobody likes all four of us.
没有人喜欢我们四个。
- Your Dad and I like all four of you. - We do?
- 你爸爸和我喜欢你们四个。 - 我们真的吗？
Just yesterday you said-- hey, look over there!
就在昨天你还说过——嘿，看那边！
It's something to look at!
有东西值得一看！
- Uh, Dad, we can see you.
呃，爸爸，我们能看到你。
- Ah. That's because I am not hiding,
啊。那是因为我没有藏起来，
I am looking for something I dropped earlier.
我正在找我之前掉的东西。
- You know, sweetie, maybe you just
你知道吗，亲爱的，也许你只是
need to give this Tess girl a chance.
需要给这个叫Tess的女孩一个机会。
- Ah, found 'em! [chuckles]
啊，找到了！[轻笑]
You know, Mom's right.
你知道，妈妈说得对。
You're just blowing this out of proportion.
你只是把这件事夸大了。
I mean, nobody is evil.
我是说，没有人是邪恶的。
- Hello, Thomas.
你好，Thomas。
- Evil!
- 邪恶！
- Kids, this is Rod "Dinna-ma-tey."
- 孩子们，这是Rod 'Dinna-ma-tey'。
- It's pronounced "Dynamite."
- 应该念作'Dynamite'。
as in, "Rod is... Dynamite." boom.
就像说，'Rod是... Dynamite'。砰。
- Pleasure to meet-- - [gibberish]
- 很高兴见到-- - [胡言乱语]
Rod is my old nemesis.
Rod是我的老对手。
We used to compete against each other on the ice.
我们过去常常在冰上互相对抗。
And yes, I know my pants are down.
是的，我知道我的裤子掉了。
- Cool, you guys played hockey?
- 酷，你们打冰球吗？
- Better. We were ice dancers.
- 更棒。我们是冰上舞者。
- Instead of sticks and pucks,
- 我们不用冰球棍和冰球，
we scored with sequins and pizzazz!
我们用亮片和活力得分！
- Before you kids were born, your father and I
- 在你们出生之前，你们的父亲和我
were one dance away from becoming national champions.
距离成为全国冠军只差一支舞。
- [chuckles] - It was a glorious time.
- [轻笑] - 那是一个辉煌的时期。
Your mom was the best ice dancer in the world,
你们的妈妈是世界上最好的冰舞者，
and I had the best ice dancing hair in the world,
而我拥有世界上最好的冰舞发型，
but then it all changed...
但后来一切都变了...
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
From the minute I met Rod,
从我遇见Rod的那一刻起，
I knew there was something wrong with that dude.
我知道那家伙有点问题。
There is something wrong with that dude.
那家伙有点问题。
[cheers and applause]
欢呼和掌声
Rod and Tiffany knew they couldn't beat us,
罗德和蒂芙尼知道他们赢不了我们，
for we were...
因为我们就是...
The Dancing Harpers!
舞动的哈珀斯！
[cheers and applause]
欢呼和掌声
♪ ♪
We were about to unveil, for the first time ever,
我们即将首次展示，
the incredibly dangerous "Lady-twirl."
极其危险的“女士旋转”。
Now, normally, the man twirls the woman,
通常情况下，是男人旋转女人，
but we were about to break the ice ceiling
但我们即将打破常规，
by having your mother twirl me.
让你的母亲来旋转我。
- Yes, yes.
- 是的，是的。
- We were lady-twirling our way to ice dancing history.
- 我们正以女士旋转的方式，
Whee!
哇！
Until--
直到--
- Yes! Ah!
- 是的！啊！
- Oh! - [whimpers]
- 哦！- [呜咽]
- Ahh!
- 啊！
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
[crowd gasps]
[人群惊呼]
Ahh! Ahh!
啊！啊！
Story over. Pants coming up.
故事结束。裤子提起来。
- You're a ch'liar.
- 你是个骗子。
That's a cheater and a liar.
那是作弊和撒谎。
- It's in the Dicky-tionary! - Look it up! - Hey, hey, hey. There's no need to name-call.
- 这在迪基词典里有！ - 查查看！ - 嘿，嘿，嘿。没必要骂人。
The Harpers always take the high road.
哈珀家总是走高尚路线。
- Hi-dee-hi, Harpers!
- 嗨-迪-嗨，哈珀家！
- Ch'liar! - Ahh!
- 骗子！ - 啊！
All right, Dynamite. What do you want?
好吧，Dynamite，你想要什么？
- Well, can't one ice dancer visit another ice dancer
嗯，难道一个冰舞者就不能拜访另一个冰舞者，只是为了打个招呼吗？
just to say hi? - No.
不行。
- Well, then can one ice dancer let another ice dancer know
那，一个冰舞者能不能让另一个冰舞者知道，他们要在街对面开一家体育用品店
that they're opening up their own sporting goods store
这将会让第二个冰舞者破产呢？
down the street that's gonna put the second ice dancer
好吧，这个你可以告诉我。[轻笑]
out of business?
等等，什么？
- All right, that you can do. [chuckles]
轰的一声，Dynamite来了。
Wait, what?
Tiffany？
- And boom goes the Dynamite.
是的，好吧，这种游戏两个人都能玩！
Tiffany?
蒂芙尼？
- Yeah, well, two can play at that game!
是啊，两个人也能玩这个游戏！
Anne!
安妮！
- It's--it's okay. I don't think he saw it.
没事的，我觉得他没看到。
- Oh, I saw it, and I also saw these socks.
哦，我看到了，还有这些袜子。
Rod likey. Rod takey.
罗德喜欢。罗德拿走。
- [grunts]
哼！
That's it.
就这样。
He took my hair, he took my pride,
他拿走了我的头发，拿走了我的骄傲，
he took those tube socks,
拿走了那些长筒袜，
but he's not gonna take my business.
但他休想夺走我的生意。
- Now, who wants to help mommy and Daddy
- 现在，谁想帮妈妈和爸爸
obliterate the evil enemy?
消灭那个邪恶的敌人？
You know, in a high road kind of way.
你知道的，用一种高尚的方式。
All: I do!
所有人：我愿意！
- Anne, get me my sellin' skates.
- 安妮，把我的销售滑冰鞋拿来。
It's time to put the competition on ice.
是时候让竞争对手出局了。
[phone ringing]
[电话铃响]
- Speaking of evil, I'm getting fake-timed by the fake-face.
- 说到邪恶，我正被假面人拖延时间。
Well, I can do a fake-face too.
好吧，我也可以来个假面。
Hey, nutty fudge bomb!
嘿，疯狂的巧克力炸弹！
- No, you're the nutty fudge bomb!
不，你才是疯狂的巧克力炸弹！
- No, you are!
不，你是！
I hate her.
我恨她。
What's up, buddy?
怎么了，伙计？
- Well, your brother said you were struggling in Math,
嗯，你哥哥说你在数学上有些困难，
so I thought I'd come over
所以我想过来
and help you study for tomorrow's test.
帮你准备明天的考试。
I'll bring tacos!
我会带塔可饼！
- Sounds great! Bye!
听起来不错！再见！
Ugh, tacos? Seriously?
哎，tacos？真的吗？
- But you love tacos.
但你喜欢tacos啊。
- I know! She's evil.
我知道！她太坏了。
- How'd the math test go?
数学考试怎么样？
- I got an A.
我得了A。
- Hey, "quadresties." that's quadruplet besties.
嘿，“quadresties”，就是四胞胎好朋友。
- She's almost completely fluent in Dicky.
她几乎完全精通Dicky语言。
- So what are you guys doing after school?
那你们放学后做什么？
- We're brainstorming ideas
我们正在集思广益，
to help boost sales at our parents' store.
帮助提高我们父母店里的销售额。
You know, grown-up business stuff.
你知道，大人的那些商业事务。
- And then we're gonna ride bikes!
- 然后我们要骑自行车！
- Well, if you guys really want to help boost business,
- 嗯，如果你们真的想帮助提升生意，
you should make a commercial for the store.
你们应该为商店制作一个广告。
- That's sweet, Tess,
- 那很好，Tess，
but between the brainstorming and the bike riding,
但在头脑风暴和骑自行车之间，
I don't think we have the time.
我不认为我们有时间。
- Don't be silly. We can do it right now.
- 别傻了。我们现在就可以做。
Okay, each of you tell me
好吧，你们每个人告诉我
why your Dad's store is the best store ever.
为什么你们爸爸的商店是世界上最好的商店。
- Shopping at Tom's Get Sporty will show you why
在汤姆的Get Sporty购物，你会明白为什么
it stinks to shop at our competitors.
在竞争对手那里购物真是糟糕透顶。
- Lights, camera, love it!
灯光，摄像，太喜欢了！
- You love that? Love this.
你喜欢那个？那你一定会喜欢这个。
Get Sporty rocks!
Get Sporty太棒了！
All those other stores?
那些其他商店？
What a joke.
真是笑话。
- Handsome and talented.
既英俊又有才华。
Nicky?
尼基？
- Give me a second to warm up the lips.
给我点时间热热嘴。
Box of biscuits. Box of biscuits.
饼干盒。饼干盒。
[shudders]
[颤抖]
You've had the worst. Now shop at the best!
你已经体验过最差的。现在来最好的商店购物！
- Goose bumps. Dawn?
- 鸡皮疙瘩。Dawn？
- No, I can't. I'm sorry, I'm not buying it.
- 不，我不能。对不起，我不买账。
- Not buying what?
- 不买什么？
- I'm not buying any of it!
- 我什么都不买！
You're up to something and I'm gonna find out what it is.
你肯定在搞什么鬼，我会查出来的。
- Can I do another take with my shirt off?
- 我可以再拍一次，脱掉衬衫吗？
- What is gonna draw in customers?
- 什么能吸引顾客？
Think big!
想得大一点！
- Ooh! We could adopt
- 哦！我们可以领养
a family of monkeys to work the cash registers.
一群猴子来操作收银机。
- Smaller.
- 小一点。
- Little monkeys?
- 小猴子？
- Mom! Dad! Where are you?
- 妈妈！爸爸！你们在哪里？
- What's up?
- 怎么了？
- We found a way for you the beat the Dynamites.
- 我们找到了让你打败Dynamites的方法。
- Ugh! "Dinna-ma-teys."
- 呃！“Dinna-ma-teys。”
- By making a commercial for our store.
- 通过为我们店制作一个广告。
- Oh, a commercial. I'll book the monkeys.
哦，广告。我去安排猴子们。
Hey, uh, Carl, project... [imitating chimp]
嘿，呃，卡尔，项目……[模仿猩猩]
is a go.
开始了。
- No, Dad. We already shot the commercial.
不，爸爸。我们已经拍完广告了。
- Oh, yeah. Uh...
哦，对。呃……
Sorry, Carl. I know I promised
对不起，卡尔。我知道我承诺过
this would never happen again, but it happened again.
这种事不会再发生，但它又发生了。
Carl?
卡尔？
- When did you guys shoot a commercial?
你们什么时候拍的广告？
- Today at school with our friend, Tess.
今天在学校和我们朋友，泰丝一起拍的。
Who is not evil.
她不是坏人。
- And doesn't want anything from us.
- 而且对我们没有所图。
- And is the best director I've ever worked with.
- 她是我合作过的最好的导演。
- Wow.
- 哇。
Is it possible my chickstincts were wrong?
难道我的直觉错了吗？
That Tess' face really isn't fake?
难道Tess的脸真的不是假的？
- Oh, hi.
- 哦，嗨。
You caught me pulling up my tube socks.
你正好看到我在拉起我的袜子。
I'm ice dancing champion, Rod Dynamite...
我是冰舞冠军，Rod Dynamite...
And welcome to my new sporting goods store,
欢迎来到我的新体育用品店，
Get Sporty... [voice echoing] Er! Er! Er!
运动起来... [声音回响] 呃！呃！呃！
- That place looks just like our store!
那地方看起来就像我们的店！
- Why Get Sporty when you Get Sporty-er?
既然要运动，为何不更运动一点？
[voice echoing] Er! Er!
[声音回响] 呃！呃！
Don't believe me? Then listen to my competitor's own children.
不信我？那就听听我竞争对手自己孩子的评价。
- Tom's Get Sporty-- what a joke.
汤姆的运动用品店——真是个笑话。
- Tom's Get Sporty-- stinks.
汤姆的运动用品店——烂透了。
- Box of biscuits. Box of biscuits.
一盒饼干。一盒饼干。
- I guess that's what they sell over at Tom's Get Sporty.
我想那就是他们在汤姆的运动用品店卖的东西。
And Dawn, what do you think about those overpriced items
道恩，你怎么看你爸爸店里那些价格过高的商品？
at your Dad's store?
- I'm not buying any of it!
- And neither should you!
So come on down to Get Sporty-er!
[voice echoing] Er! Er!
- [growls]
- Owned and operated by ice dancing champions,
Rod Dynamite... - Tiffany Dynamite,
and our beautiful daughter... - Tess Dynamite!
- Yes! I was right!
She's a total fake-face!
她是个彻头彻尾的假面人！
Whoo-hoo! This is such a personal victory!
呜呼！这真是个人的胜利！
And a huge loss for the family.
这对家族来说是个巨大的损失。
- That's it. He crossed the line.
就是这样。他越界了。
He used my kids and my tube socks against me.
他利用我的孩子和我的袜子对付我。
- Don't worry, Tom. I know what to do.
别担心，汤姆。我知道该怎么做。
Now, where can I get my hands on some Dinna-ma-tey?
现在，我该去哪里弄些Dinna-ma-tey呢？
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇。
What happened to "Harpers always take the high road"?
“哈珀家的人总是走高尚之路”怎么了？
- Oh, the high road is closed for construction,
哦，高尚之路正在施工，
but the low road is wide open, baby.
但低路却是畅通无阻的，宝贝。
- Maybe for them,
- 或许对他们来说，
but my chickstincts tell me that we're better than that,
但我的直觉告诉我，我们比那更好，
and as you all know, my chickstincts are never wrong.
而且你们都知道，我的直觉从不出错。
Say it with me.
跟我一起说。
All: Dawn's chickstincts are never wrong.
全体: Dawn的直觉从不出错。
- And that's my new ring tone.
- 那将成为我的新铃声。
All: Dawn's chickstincts are never wrong.
全体: Dawn的直觉从不出错。
- Ahh, it's the little things.
- 啊，就是这些小事。
♪ ♪
- By the way...
- 顺便说一句...
[sniffs] I know you're a mannequin.
[嗅] 我知道你是个假人模特。
Oh! Ha! [babbling]
哦！哈！[喃喃自语]
- Oh, I finally got my monkey! [chuckles]
- 哦，我终于得到我的猴子了！[轻笑]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- Ladies and gentlemen, customers of all ages!
- 女士们、先生们，各年龄段的顾客们！
Introducing something you won't find at the less-er store.
推出你在其他店里找不到的东西。
Get Sporty's new in-store zip-line!
体验Sporty的新店内滑索！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- Thank you, thank you. You're so kind.
- 谢谢，谢谢。你们真是太好了。
[chuckles] All right, here we go!
[轻笑] 好了，我们开始吧！
Ah! Ahh! Ahh!
啊！啊！啊！
Ahh! Oh! - Oh!
啊！哦！- 哦！
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
哦，哦，哦。
- Are you--oh! - [whimpers like a chimp]
- 你是不是——哦！- [像猩猩一样呜咽]
- It looks like all they're doing over here
- 看起来他们在这里
is monkey-ing around.
只是在胡闹。
Now who's ready to do some serious savings,
现在谁准备好
down at Get Sporty-er?
在Get Sporty-er进行一些真正的省钱了？
[all chattering]
[大家都在议论]
- Dinna-ma-tey!
- 迪纳玛泰！
Whoa! - Oh, Tom!
哇！ - 哦，汤姆！
- That's it.
- 就是这样。
It's low road time.
走低路的时候到了。
- This is the end of the yellow brick Rod.
- 这是黄砖路的尽头。
Shop away, my pretties!
尽情购物吧，我的宝贝们！
- Welcome!
- 欢迎！
So how'd it go, Ice Man?
那么，进展如何，冰人？
- Like taking candy from a big, bald baby.
- 就像从一个大光头宝宝手里拿糖一样简单。
- I can't believe they actually thought I was their friend.
- 我真不敢相信他们居然以为我是他们的朋友。
Seriously?
真的吗？
Who could possibly like all of them?
谁能喜欢他们所有人呢？
- Huh. - Or any of them?
或者说，谁能喜欢他们中的任何一个？
[laughter]
[笑声]
All: [sigh]
[众人叹气]
- Oh, now what?
哦，现在又怎么了？
Dawn, I am so, so sorry.
道恩，我非常、非常抱歉。
- Don't "I'm so, so sorry" me, fake-face.
别用那张假面脸对我说‘我非常、非常抱歉’。
You're gonna pay for what you've done.
你会为你所做的付出代价的。
Wow, this place looks exactly like my parents' store.
哇，这个地方看起来跟我父母的店一模一样。
- Okay, I know you won't believe me,
好吧，我知道你不会相信我，
but my Dad stole my phone to make his mean old commercial.
但我爸偷了我的手机来拍他那讨厌的老广告。
I had nothing to do with it. - [scoffs]
我与此事无关。
Give me a break.
饶了我吧。
- Oh, can we please just sit down and talk about it?
哦，我们能不能坐下来谈谈这件事？
- I don't want to sit down and talk about-- you have massage chairs?
我不想坐下来谈——你们有按摩椅吗？
- Dawn, your friendship is super important.
Dawn，你的友谊对我非常重要。
You have to believe me.
你一定要相信我。
- Well, I don't believe--
嗯，我不相信——
y-- [humming]
呃——
Ooh-ahh.
哦-啊。
No, you're lying.
不，你在撒谎。
- I would never lie to my quadrestie.
我绝不会对我的好朋友撒谎。
You're so stressed.
你压力好大。
- Well, I'm sorry, but I just can't--
嗯，对不起，但我真的不能--
what is happening to my face?
我的脸怎么了？
- Well...
嗯...
- Goose.
鹅。
- Guys, good news.
伙计们，好消息。
Turns out Tess is completely innocent.
结果证明Tess是完全无辜的。
Both: What?
两人：什么？
- Ugh, out of polish. B-r-b!
- 哎呀，指甲油没了。马上回来！
- Can't w-a-i-t!
- 等不及了！
- What happened to your chickstincts?
- 你的直觉怎么了？
- Oh, they're working.
- 哦，它们还在运作。
Quaddle up.
准备好了。
I know she's not innocent.
我知道她不是无辜的。
I'm only here to dig up dirt on Get Sporty-er
我来这里只是为了挖掘Get Sporty-er的污点
so we can destroy them. - Oh.
这样我们就可以摧毁他们。 - 哦。
- Fake-face thinks she can fake her way to victory?
假面以为她能靠假扮赢得胜利？
Two can play at that game.
两个人可以玩这个游戏。
- No, four can.
不，四个人可以。
[vibrating]
[振动]
- Oh, or three.
哦，或者三个人。
You guys got this, right?
你们能搞定，对吧？
♪ ♪
- Oh, here you go. How you feeling, honey?
哦，给你。感觉怎么样，亲爱的？
- Horrible. - Oh.
糟糕透了。
- First he took my hair, now he took my smile.
他先是拿走了我的头发，现在又夺走了我的笑容。
He's a monster!
他是怪物！
- Mom! Dad!
妈妈！爸爸！
We found a way to beat out Get Sporty-er!
我们找到了打败Get Sporty-er的方法！
You know those recalled cans of tennis balls
你们知道那些被召回的网球罐
you sent back to China last month?
你们上个月寄回中国的吗？
- The ones that explode at 100 degrees?
那些在100度会爆炸的？
- Rod's selling them.
Rod在卖它们。
- So all we have to do is tell everybody Rod sells dangerous balls.
所以我们只需要告诉大家Rod卖危险球。
Then, they'll come back to our store.
然后，他们就会回到我们的店里。
- Look kids, I appreciate it.
孩子们，我很感激。
[all shudder]
[大家都颤抖了一下]
But it's over.
但一切都结束了。
When you fight someone who plays dirty,
当你与一个不择手段的人战斗时，
the only way to win is to not fight.
唯一取胜的方法就是不要战斗。
- So tomorrow, after the dentist--
- 所以明天，看完牙医之后--
We are going to the dentist.
我们要去看牙医。
Then we're going to Get Sporty-er
然后我们去Get Sporty-er
to tell Rod and Tiffany that they've won.
告诉Rod和Tiffany他们赢了。
Then we can just get on with our lives
这样我们就可以继续我们的生活
and no one else has to get hurt.
而且不会再有人受伤。
I've already lost enough of your Dad.
我已经失去了太多关于你爸爸的事情。
I don't want us to lose anymore.
我不想我们再失去更多了。
- [wincing] - Oh.
- [痛苦地皱眉] - 哦。
Ooh! - Oh!
哦！- 哦！
- I can't believe they're just giving up.
- 我简直不敢相信他们就这样放弃了。
- They might be, but we aren't.
- 他们可能会，但我们不会。
- What a dump.
- 真是个破地方。
This store is horrible.
这家店太糟糕了。
- It looks just like ours.
- 看起来跟我们的一模一样。
- It's horrible!
- 太糟糕了！
Sorry.
对不起。
Let's take the ice, hon.
我们拿冰块吧，亲爱的。
- Okay, you guys ready? All: Ready.
好了，你们准备好了吗？
- Go.
准备好了。
- Now, I am humbled to introduce,
开始。
all the way from Washington, D.C.,
现在，我很荣幸地介绍，
Get Sporty-er's most powerful customer
来自华盛顿特区，
and my close, personal friend...
Get Sporty-er最强大的顾客
President Barack Obama.
以及我的亲密个人朋友...
[cheers and applause]
巴拉克·奥巴马总统。
- Boom.
嘭。
Look-alike.
长得像。
Well, well.
哎呀，哎呀。
Lookie here.
看这里。
Keep the cameras on for this one, boys.
把镜头对准这里，伙计们。
It's gonna be a doozy.
这将会是个大场面。
- [clears throat] Uh, Rod, Tiffany.
嗯，Rod，Tiffany。
Uh, Mr. President.
呃，总统先生。
Um...
嗯...
Uh, we just came here today to say...
呃，我们今天来这里只是想说...
- No, you can do it, go. - Okay.
- 不，你可以的，说吧。 - 好的。
- You win.
- 你赢了。
- Sorry, I couldn't hear that through the hair.
- 抱歉，头发太厚，我听不清。
- [sighs] You win!
- [叹气] 你赢了！
[teeth dropping on the floor] Both: [gasp]
[牙齿掉在地上] 两人: [惊呼]
Sweetie, I would appreciate if you picked up my teeth.
亲爱的，如果你能帮我捡起牙齿，我会很感激。
- Of course.
- 当然。
Here. - Thank you.
给你。 - 谢谢。
- Now, can we please just agree that this town is big enough for two sporting goods stores?
- 现在，我们能不能同意这个镇子足够大，容得下两家体育用品店？
- Deal?
- 成交？
- Deal.
成交。
Ha! - No!
哈！
Dynamites don't deal. Tiff?
不！
Ahh.
炸药不讲条件。蒂芙？
- Dad, why's it getting so hot in here?
啊。
- It must be from the scorching hot deals
爸爸，为什么这里变得这么热？
here at Get Sporty-er! Am I right?
一定是来自Get Sporty-er这里火热的大促销！我说得对吗？
- Or because you guys just got burned.
或者是因为你们刚刚被烧了。
- What's he doing next to my thermostat?
他在我的温控器旁边做什么？
- Probably the same thing that he's doing.
可能和他正在做的事情一样。
And him.
还有他。
And me, when I set that one to 100 degrees.
还有我，当我把那个调到100度的时候。
Get your cameras ready for this one, boys.
准备好你们的相机，伙计们。
It'd gonna be even doozy-er.
这将更加惊人。
- No.
不。
[tennis balls exploding] [people screaming]
[网球爆炸] [人们尖叫]
- I love you, kids!
我爱你们，孩子们！
[balls exploding] [people screaming]
[球爆炸] [人们尖叫]
- Cover me, fake Obama!
掩护我，假奥巴马！
- [screams]
[尖叫]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
Ew, your hair! [screams]
哎呀，你的头发！[尖叫]
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- Ew, your face!
- 哎呀，你的脸！
- Oh! It's the heat!
- 哦！是热气！
I'm melting! [sobs]
我在融化！[啜泣]
- Now, that's a fake-face.
- 现在，那是个假脸。
- Oh! - [sizzle]
- 哦！- [嘶嘶声]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- You win.
- 你赢了。
- I'm--I'm sorry.
- 我很抱歉。
I couldn't hear you over the glare.
你的光芒太耀眼，我听不清你说什么。
[laughs]
[笑]
Wow, you did not age well.
哇，你看起来可没怎么变老。
Dancing Harpers.
跳舞的吟游诗人。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
[发声]
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ 哼唱 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪
- ♪
♪